http://www.parksassociates.com/policy

Providing market intelligence for more than 30 years
CompanyMeet The TeamAnalyst BlogContact UsResearchIndustry ReportsConsumer AnalyticsNewslettersResearch ServicesPrimary ResearchWhitepapersConsumer Data SearchNewsroomPress ReleasesAnalyst BlogIn The NewsEventsConnected Health SummitCONNECTIONS™ EuropeCONNECTIONS™ USCONNECTIONS™ SummitFuture of VideoSmart Energy SummitWebinars and WorkshopsUpcoming Industry EventsPremier ProgramContact
Login
Register
Cart (0)
Return, Refund, and Cancellation Policies
Parks Associates does not provide returns, refunds, or cancellation of orders for its research or event products once they have been delivered to the buyer’s reading room. If you are unsatisfied with any of the content delivered, please contact Parks Associates at 972-490-1113 or sales@parksassociates.com to discuss.
....
Deliverables and Delivery Policy
Upon confirmation of your purchase, an electronic copy of the purchased content, typically a PDF or PowerPoint file, will appear in your online Reading Room. You can view and download this file at your discretion. Past Webcasts include a PDF of the presentation with a link to the archived audio and login instructions.
....
Parks Associates’ Privacy Policy
Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services.
What Information Do We Collect?
When you visit our Web site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site.
1. Personal Information You Choose to Provide
Registration Information.
You will provide us information about yourself, your firm or company, and your practices when you register for certain services, download Parks Associates latest white papers, or register for email newsletters and alerts.
Email Information.
If you choose to correspond with us through email and check off the box affirming interest in receiving email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. This practice follows GDPR laws.
2. Web Site Use Information
How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?
Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering and expanding our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. You may notify us at any time if you do not wish to receive these offers by emailing us at info@parksassociates.com
Sharing Information with Third Parties
We may enter into alliances, partnerships or other business arrangements with third parties who may be given access to personal information including your name, address, telephone number and email for the purpose of providing you information regarding products and services that we think will be of interest to you. In connection with alliances, partnerships or arrangements, we may also provide certain information to third parties if we have determined that the information will be used in a responsible manner by a responsible third party. We also use third parties to facilitate our business, including, but not limited to, sending email and processing credit card payments. In connection with these offerings and business operations, our partners and other third parties may have access to your personal information for use in connection with business activities. As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or any dissolution.
Notice of New Services and Changes
Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. As our customer, you will be given the opportunity to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by sending us an email request at info@parksassociates.com.
Request to Delete Your Contact Details
Parks Associates will delete any contact details within our database by request. As our customer, you can notify us of your desire to have data deleted by emailing us at info@parksassociates.com or calling our headquarters at +1-972-490-1113.
How Do We Protect Your Information?
How Do We Secure Information Transmissions?
Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send private information to us by email. Some of the information you may enter on our Web site may be transmitted securely via Secure Sockets Layer SSL, 128 bit encryption services. Pages utilizing this technology will have URLs that start with HTTPS instead of HTTP. Please contact info@parksassociates.com if you have any questions or concerns.
How Can You Access and Correct Your Information?
You may request access to all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in our database by emailing info@parksassociates.com
Certain Disclosures
We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law or comply with legal process served on us or affiliated parties; (b) protect and defend our rights and property, our site, the users of our site, and/or our affiliated parties; (c) act under circumstances to protect the safety of users of our site, us, or third parties.
What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?
We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Web site.
Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Web site to another Web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other Web site, including Web sites which have a link on our Web site, is subject to that Web site's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.
Your Consent
By using our Web site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our Web site to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it.
....
Analyst Blog
Navigating a New World: COVID-19 Impact on Video Viewing
12/11/20
OTT Partnerships: Key to Success
12/10/20
How Connectivity Issues are being resolved in the Smart Home
12/10/20
Press Releases
Nearly one in ten US broadband households cancelled at least one video service during the COVID-19 crisis12/10/20
47% of US broadband households subscribe to Amazon Prime Video12/09/20
Churn rate drops to 38% among OTT services and 49% among vMVPDs 12/08/20
Company
Meet The TeamAnalyst BlogContact Us
Newsroom
Parks AssociatesCompanyResearchNewsroomEventsContactLogin
Research
Industry ReportsConsumer AnalyticsNewslettersResearch ServicesPrimary ResearchWhitepapersConsumer Data Search
Events
Connected Health SummitCONNECTIONS™ EuropeCONNECTIONS™ USCONNECTIONS™ SummitFuture of VideoSmart Energy SummitWebinars and WorkshopsUpcoming Industry EventsPremier Program
Account
Order HistoryProfileReading RoomPassword
Newsletters
Subscribe Today
Policies
Refund & Privacy
© 1998-2020 Parks Associates. All Rights Reserved.
